Thanks for your time
News Anchor
Thank you for your time
Is today your debut press conference?
Yes, sir.
Yes, it is.
Since your unveiling at Kanda Myojin Hall?
Yes.
Yes, it has.
It's been a long time.
It's been two years.
Do you have any memories of the unveiling?
It wasn't like we were all really close like we are now.
I didn't know where to be.
I didn't know who to talk to.
I didn't know what to do.
A day full of things I didn't know anymore
You were always tense and nervous.
Isn't this the first time you've met?
Almost first meeting
Almost.
A couple of times.
Is this the first time you've met a girl you haven't seen at an audition?
It's about the first time.
It's not the first time.
No, it's the first time we've met.
It was our first time meeting.
First time you've met her?
Yes, ma'am.
Audition.
All the potentials have never met before.
All the other potentials had never met before.
Don't talk to anyone.
And with this...
Soon will come the first meeting
Already.
already
queuing
It's so funny now that I think about it
We're such an open book.
I feel like I'm going to be filled
It's a lively backstage area.
You've changed in two years.
You've changed
I want to be really happy about it.
I heard that two years ago, Sunday press conference was stiff.
I don't even feel like it.
No, but when the name "Nyari Equals JOY" was announced.
When the name JOY was announced, they asked me what I thought about it.
They asked me what I thought about it.
I couldn't really think of anything else to say at the time, and I said, "Oh, it's nice and deep.
I said, "Oh, it's nice and deep. I answered, "What is it?
I will do my best to speak properly today.
Yes, two years ago, when I was being interviewed or asked a question for the first time, I didn't know why I should answer,
Two years ago, when I was asked a question for the first time in an interview, I didn't know why I should answer it, and I sometimes wished someone else would answer it for me,
But this time, I will be able to use my experience of the past two years to answer questions on my own.
I'm looking forward to the soak session.
I will do my best.
I guess you are going to hold your debut press conference now, right?
Yes, my debut press conference.
It's the first time for me to make my debut, and I'm standing up in front of the press today,
I felt a little bit of the tension from that time.
Yes, I am.
I am nervous.
Nervous?
I'm nervous.
I just stood on stage at the rehearsal for the unveiling, and I haven't seen the stage since the unveiling.
I thought it was nostalgic.
Did you two meet before the unveiling?
I don't know if it was before the unveiling or during the dance screening for the final audition. When you went to the dance screening for the final audition?
You were together?
They were in the same slot.
They were dancing together.
It's a youthful sublimation.
I didn't realize it at the time.
We met at that time.
Then there, it's a case of meeting at the dance screening.
I think it was shown in the documentary that Alice was so nervous that she cried during the unveiling.
I think she was the most nervous from the very beginning, but I don't think she ever cries because of nervousness.
I don't think I will ever cry from nervousness.
I don't think I will cry from now on.
You are cool.
I became stronger and stronger.
But that time, she suddenly started crying.
Transparent.
I was so worried, thinking that an incredibly pretty, beautiful girl was crying, and I wondered what was wrong.
Alice was so cool too. She was so majestic.
She was so nervous. I don't understand Japanese anymore when I get nervous.
Do you have a special place in your heart for this venue?
The machine room.
There was no place, it was a little bit spacious with sofas.
A little bit spacious.
Yes, it is.
I knew it.
I cried there.
Before it started.
Yes.
I cried before it started. When it started, I felt like I was Alice of the Mountain, and I felt at ease.
Today, with a smile.
I'll do my best.
Please do your best.
Yes.
Yes, I will do my best.
Yes, that's good.
Yes, I will do my best socially.
Now then, let's send alternative d Twitter to you. Please, everyone.
Thank you very much for watching.
Thank you for watching.
First of all, let's hear Julie Hazama's too reckless wish for Fingerprints, please.
Yes, Mr. Sashihara, I'm sure, I'm sure, please produce a drama in Miyagi.
Drama?
I'm so sorry.
The bigger the dream, the better.
As for recklessness, I love the Majisuka Gakuen series that AKB and others have done.
I also love "Cabasca Gakuen".
That brings back memories.
I used to watch it when I was in kindergarten.
What?
When I was in kindergarten.
When you were in kindergarten?
I see.
I watched it when I was in kindergarten.
I'd like to play a unique character with everyone someday.
I see.
I'm counting on you.
I understand.
So, Sashihara-san, have you decided on your decision?
It has been decided.
Pending.
Ehhhh...
Suddenly
Eeeee...
There's a good reason for what we've done!
Of course I want to see a drama in which everyone's appearance is carefully characterized one by one!
I'd like to see it, but I've never done a drama before.
You've done a lot of work as a writer and scriptwriter.
But I'm a little too much into variety.
I'd be happy to produce a variety show for you.
But drama...
I'm not sure I'm up to it right now, so please put it on hold.
I'm still in shock that I watched it when I was in kindergarten, and it still haunts me.
I don't think I can make it happen.
Someday...
I'll make it happen
How do you feel about this, Aida?
I'll do my best so that one day you'll produce not only dramas but also variety shows.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much
Next, Ms. Ayumi Ichihara.
Ayumi Ichihara
Ms. Mitsuki Oshida
Yuka Murayama.
On behalf of the three of you, Ms. Murayama, please.
Yes, ma'am.
Sashihara-san, I'm sure, I'm sure. Please give me Sashihara-san's clothes.
Oh, I see, hand-me-downs.
Sashihara-san wears all kinds of clothes.
I would like to use this as motivation to become a wonderful woman like the wonderful Sashihara-san.
Ms. Oshida, please tell us more about this request.
Yes, I have never been familiar with clothes and cosmetics, and I started makeup when I entered this world, but I still don't know a lot about it, so I wanted to take some of Ms. Sashihara's wonderful sense of style to help me become a more beautiful woman.
May I ask why, Ichihara-san?
Yes, I know that I have been doing my makeup with the help of Sashihara-san.
Yes, I'd like to have Sashihara-san's osadori so that I can always feel Sashihara-san's touch.
I'm so happy, but it's heavy.
I really want anything.
Anything.
Even a sock. I'll wear it every day.
I understand.
What shall we do then? Do you think it'll be okay, Mr. Fingerstalker?
Okay, it's decided. What's your decision, Fingerbrain?
I'm withholding. There's a good reason.
The reason is... I'm more mature now.
I wear high-brand clothes.
I don't want to look like Gucci.
So for now, please give it to my sister Equal Love and my sister Noemie.
I'll give my Gucci to Murashige.
I'll give it to you when you're older.
Now that you've said those kind words, I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
I'll try to wear it someday.
And now, Ms. Esmilenko, Mr. Sashkala.
Yes, I'm sure. I'm sure.
When you turn 20, please race boats with me.
Boat racing is my big boom right now.
I've been watching boat races on Equalab, and I've been thinking how fun it would be.
I can't do it yet, right? When I turn 20, I'll make my debut in both boat races.
I'm hoping that when I turn 20 we can both make our boat racing debut together.
It's hard to decide. I'm giving away so many gifts.
I'm having fun. I'm having fun. I'm having fun in a planned way.
I'm having fun, as long as it's reasonable.
It's fun, but... Yes, I understand.
Then, please make a decision for Esme, Mr. Sashuhara.
Let's make it happen.
There's nothing wrong with having fun as long as you do it within the limits of what you really enjoy, and it's fun.
The next time I'm here, I'm actually going to be in a commercial for the Boat Race, so...
So we're making memories to commemorate the event.
So, as part of making memories, let's have fun together without getting too carried away.
Thank you very much.
I don't know much about the commemorative edition, but I'm sure we can learn a lot together.
I appreciate your kind words so much... can I call you when I turn 20?
Of course, let's do it with that scholarship.
Yes, sir.
Up to 100 yen per race.
Thank you very much.
Next, we have Momoka Yamada.
Let's hear Momoka Yamada's reckless wish for Sashihara-san.
Sashihara-san, I'm sure you'll do my makeup for me when the time comes.
Makeup?
Yes, ma'am.
I see.
I've been referring to the amazing makeup techniques that Sashihara-san introduces on her youtube channel, so please give my best wishes to Sashihara-san.
Please give my best regards to Ms. Sashihara.
I would like you to produce this makeup.
I see.
Okay, it's decided.
Okay, Sashihara-san, please give us your decision.
Pending.
No, I'm told that everyone is definitely more interested in the latest makeup values, so I'd like you to do the latest idiosyncratic makeup, because it's the first makeup of the newest and the most advanced.
Everyone pays attention to each and every part, part by part.
Because right now, I'm only in love with the rarest of places.
Isn't it delicious?
Please do it in a uniform way.
I'd love to know everyone's latest makeup.
Please tell us.
I'll do my best.
I'll put it on hold.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure you guys know more about it than I do.
Yes, I will continue to watch you on YouTube, etc.
Please let me know.
I'll keep my antenna up for your channel cosmetics information too!
Thank you very much.
Yes, I know it's late, but thank you so much for joining us today.
From my point of view as a producer, this is a wonderful group.
I think we have become a cool group and a cute group.
Including Ornithia who is currently on a leave of absence.
I believe that all of you will become a bigger and bigger idol group.
I will do my best to make it happen.
Thank you very much for today.
Here we go.
Y!
I'm back to the place of memories!
I'm back!
See you soon!
Maybe I'll see you.
I'll see you
Hardly.
I'm already here.
Aoi, Ayumi, me.
Lennon.
Alice lined up in that order.
But we were all too shy to say a word.
Why is Mizuki's hair so short?
It's so short.
Have you been growing it long since then?
I've been growing it out.
For two years.
That's for sure.
I remember everything so vividly, who was sitting where.
I remember everything so vividly.
It's like a dream now.
Thank you all for your hard work at today's press conference.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure you have a lot of memories in this room.
I watched it for two years.
I miss it.
I took another picture of this background.
And who was sitting where.
I remember.
This is Ayumi's first time here.
Welcome.
Hi.
I've been watching... everyone else's.
It's a documentary, so the moment I walked in...
The moment you walked in, you were like, "Let's work hard here.
You seem excited.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
Do you have any memories of this room?
I'd love to hear.
But Alice really started crying right before the press conference.
So I remember saying, "Let's work around here," and we did it like this.
That's great.
I remember she started crying even though her makeup was done, and the makeup artist was in a hurry to put her down.
Now here's the thing.
Everyone's story.
It's fun.
Two year memory.
That's great.
Julie's on the myofascial roller, too.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I'm thinking, that's what I'm thinking today.
Oh, why are you all jumping out of your skin?
Oh, yeah.
If I had a scene from the unveiling of the myofascial roller.
I've got the one that relaxes the muscles.
Cause you were laughing.
Emo.
And over the past two years, you've held a press conference here in Kannami Azin.
Do you have any thoughts on how it went today?
No, I don't.
But compared to two years ago, everyone was more relaxed.
I think we all did a pretty good job at the press conference.
Personally, I'm still not used to speaking in front of people.
When I speak with everyone backstage.
I'm probably the loudest person in the room.
I get nervous when I'm in front of people.
I think this is what I have to work on in my third year.
I think this is my third year's effort.
I think that's what the third year is all about.
Oh, I see.
That's it.
Third year.
The next three years, right?
Next three years.
Third year.
Yeah, so...
That's great.
Good job, Kéchan.
Good job, Ke-chan.
Let's go for it
Let's do it, let's do it
Let's do our best
I think it's almost our second anniversary and we're going to have a second anniversary concert.
I was wondering if you could make a little announcement about that.
It's going to be held on February 23rd.
Nearly Equal Joy
2nd anniversary Premium Concert
Tickets for the general public will be available until tomorrow, January 31.
Please come and see us!
We look forward to seeing you!
We'll be waiting for you.